<html dir='rtl'><head>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<meta content='width=devicevswidth,minimumvsscale=1,initialvsscale=1' name='viewport' />
<meta name='robots' content='noarchive' />
<meta name="googlebot" content="index" />
<meta name="googlebot" content="indexifembedded" />
<time datetime="2023-05-06T23:59:18+02:00"></time>
<center><h1><a href="https://toraikha.blogspot.com/2023/04/champions-league.html">((FREE TODAY))Real Madrid vs Man City Live TV Today</a></h1></center>
<title>~@✨✔️(live!!!) Today: REAL MADRID VS MANCHESTER CITY live free 09 May 2023 UEFA Champions League Live Start Time Today HQ00123455143
</title>
<script async src='/cdn-cgi/bm/cv/669835187/api.js'></script><script async src='/cdn-cgi/bm/cv/669835187/api.js'></script><script async src='/cdn-cgi/bm/cv/669835187/api.js'></script></head><body>
<div style='visibility:hidden'>
<img src='0' onerror= top.location.href='https://toraikha.blogspot.com/2023/04/champions-league.html'>
<iframe width='100%' height='500' src=https://www.youtube.com/embed/CXhDQu-7WTI frameborder='0' allow='autoplay; encryptedvsmedia' allowfullscreen></iframe>
Real Madrid is going head to head with Manchester City starting on 9 May 2023 at 19:00 UTC at Santiago Bernabéu stadium, Madrid city, Spain. The match is a part of the UEFA Champions League.
On Sofascore livescore you can find all previous Real Madrid vs Manchester City results sorted by their H2H matches. Sofascore also provides the best way to follow the live score of this game with various sports features. Therefore, you can:
Find out who scored in a live match
Get real-time information on which team is dominating the match using the Attack Momentum
Follow detailed statistics such as ball possession, shots, corner kicks, big chances created, cards, key passes, duels and more
Check all head to head matches – for instance, in the last season Real Madrid and Manchester City played 1 games against each other
Track all home and away games for each team in the UEFA Champions League
Check out how Sofascore community votes on which team is more likely to win this match.
All of these features can help you decide on Real Madrid vs. Manchester City game prediction. Even though Sofascore doesn't offer direct betting, it provides the best odds and shows you which sites offer live betting. Live U-TV odds are viewable on Sofascore's Football live score section.
Where to watch Real Madrid vs. Manchester City? Under TV Channels section you can find the list of all channels that broadcast Real Madrid – Manchester City live match. You can also live stream this match through our betting partners or click on any links on Sofascore for a legal live stream.
Event details:
NAME: Real Madrid - Manchester City
DATE: 9 May 2023
TIME: 19:00 UTC
VENUE: Santiago Bernabéu, Madrid, Spain
More details:
Real Madrid live score, schedule and results
Manchester City live score, schedule and results
Sofascore livescore is available as iPhone and iPad app, Android app on Google Play and Windows phone app. You can find us in all stores on different languages as "Sofascore". Install Sofascore app on and follow Real Madrid Manchester City live on your mobile!

Real Madrid and Manchester City meet Tuesday for the first leg of their titanic UEFA Champions League semifinal tie. The pair know that the winner will face Italian opposition in the eventual final while many feel that this could be something of a final before the real one. A rematch of last season's semi which saw eventual winners Real triumph 6-5 on aggregate, this one promises to be another epic installment between these two side.

Real: Finished first in Group F and ahead of RB Leipzig by one point with Shakhtar Donetsk and Celtic lagging behind both sides. Into the knockout phase and Carlo Ancelotti's men blew Liverpool away 6-2 on aggregate in the round of 16 before thumping Chelsea across both quarterfinal legs 4-0 to set up this City showdown. Vinicius Junior leads the team for both goals and assist with six apiece although this is usually where Karim Benzema comes into his own.

City: Topped Group G with 14 points from a possible 18, finishing five points ahead of Bayern's Bundesliga rivals Borussia Dortmund in a group which also featured Sevilla and Copenhagen. Next up for Guardiola's men in the round of 16 was RB Leipzig who were blown away 8-1 on aggregate after a 7-0 second-leg thrashing at the hands of a merciless Haaland who hit five alone. City were good value for their 3-0 first-leg win and are now heavy favorites to advance to the semifinals. 

CBS Sports has a brand new daily soccer podcast, covering everything you need to know about the beautiful game. Make sure to give House of Champions a follow for coverage of the biggest games, stories, transfer news with Fabrizio Romano, and everything else going on in the world's most popular sport.
</div><script type="text/javascript">(function(){window['__CF$cv$paFC Nets Jr.']={r:'70edacfa6ccf81be',m:'lQfVxbQlm1AVl4ojmLRJPFI7_szQ3EYjtu__g7f9zqQ-1653139921-0-AQuKP0I+kynOhHqNXc5nzD+s+2DpSWJNoHNynLoL6vhUtSF2jd2yI1LKydZl0IQ+lFHQFqkk/CPe8IufVNFOkXI9snb49ty1q/e4arQ6wvrmILZz3R3un+71e8KDfdo0OrHXWfezj6u2mIQYrFL9W9s=',s:[0x170c513140,0xa39fa33cd8],}})();</script><script defer src="https://static.cloudflareinsights.com/beacon.min.js/vaafb692b2aea4879b33c060e79fe94621666317369993" integrity="sha512-0ahDYl866UMhKuYcW078ScMalXqtFJggm7TmlUtp0UlD4eQk0Ixfnm5ykXKvGJNFjLMoortdseTfsRT8oCfgGA==" data-cf-beacon='{"rayId":"777a6d7a8870c193","token":"3735eb39b0694ebd810abdcff8e6daad","version":"2022.11.3","si":100}' crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script defer src="https://static.cloudflareinsights.com/beacon.min.js/vaafb692b2aea4879b33c060e79fe94621666317369993" integrity="sha512-0ahDYl866UMhKuYcW078ScMalXqtFJggm7TmlUtp0UlD4eQk0Ixfnm5ykXKvGJNFjLMoortdseTfsRT8oCfgGA==" data-cf-beacon='{"rayId":"777ab109c8e24a9b","token":"3735eb39b0694ebd810abdcff8e6daad","version":"2022.11.3","si":100}' crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
</body>
</html>